快说我很美
Tell me I'm beautiful.
你一直很美
You know you are.
老板来了
Boss is here.
你都听见了吧? 老板来了
Y'all hear that? The boss is here.
- 敬真理 - 真理!
- To truth. - Truth!
- 哇! - 我去转一圈
- Whoo! - Let me make some rounds.
- 宝贝 我去去就来 - 你去哪?
- Baby, I'll be back. - Where you going?
我有些小事要处理
I've got to handle some details.
那你雇的那些人干嘛?
Don't you have people for that?
这叫 "客户服务" 塔莎
It's called "customer service," Tasha.
这事我亲力亲为
I do this part myself.
你好 我要更多香槟
Excuse me, more champagne,
伏特加 还有更多其它的就酒
more vodka, more everything.
等等 等等 别走
Mm, wait, wait, hold up.
再来些鸡尾酒和龙舌兰酒
Bring some henny and bring some patron.
还没到午夜就已经有四百人了
Head count's at 400 and it's not even midnight.
火警说让我们把人数控制在三百二十五以下
Fire marshal told us to keep it under 325,
所以如果着火 我们就死定了
so if he shows up, we're fucked.
这里人山人海
Place is fucking bananas.
你还是值得冒这个险的
You might be worth the risk.
我说过 这事交给我没问题 现在我做到了
I told you, that's all behind me now, and I delivered.
这是今年最棒的的夜店开业庆典
This is the best goddamn nightclub opening
为了这事我绞尽脑汁 动用了一切关系
the whole year. My whole database turned out.
是 你功不可没 找对了人
Yeah, you know the right people.
今天是个开门红 但我们还是要认真做生意
And it's bangin' tonight, but we stay in business.
火辣音乐 性感女郎
We keep the music hot, the women hot,
还有千万别让人靠近这扇门
and make it damn near impossible  to get in this fucking door.
我的VIP们也不行?
Even for my VIP's?
拜托 去你的VIP们
Come on, fuck your VIP's.
我们要重新定义这个词
We gonna redefine the word.
老板
Boss.
嘿 老板 他们想你去次楼下
Hey, boss, they want you downstairs.
- 谁说的? - 汤米
- Who wants me? - Tommy.
我也要去吗?
Should I come too?
你在车里等着
You wait in the car.
你觉得你能他妈的从我这偷了东西
You think you can fucking steal from me
还能毫发无伤地远走高飞?
and then just walk the fuck away?
我什么也没做 大哥!
I didn't do anything, man!
她毫不知情!
She don't know nothing!
好吧! 嘿 嘿 是我偷的
Okay, look! Hey, hey, look! Hey, I stole from you.
好吗 是我偷的 求求你
Okay, it was me. Look, please, man.
好吗 这不是她的错
Okay, it's not her fault.
你说对了 米格尔
You're right there, Miguel.
这不是玛丽亚的错 是你的
It's not Maria's fault, it's yours.
你有机会改正错误的
You have your opportunity to make this right.
你只要告诉我你把我的东西藏哪了
All you have to do is tell me where you hid my shit.
我不能 我不能
I can't. I can't.
他根本没听懂我的话 玛丽亚
He's not listening to me, Maria.
来 你来对他说
Here, you talk to him.
米格尔 告诉他你用那笔钱做了什么!
他妈的发生什么事了?
What the fuck is going on?
幽灵 见见米格尔・阿尔瓦雷斯
Ghost, meet Miguel Alvarez
和他的未婚妻玛丽亚
and his fiancee Maria.
克鲁兹照例开车干活 这狗娘养的截了他的车
Cruz was driving his route when this motherfucker jumped him,
还朝他脑袋开了一枪
shot him in the head.
克鲁兹 所以他拿了...
Cruz, so he got...
钱! 一天的所有收入
the money! A whole day's paper.
- 我们拿回来没? - 没有
- We get it back? - No.
在维克多找到他之前 他已经脱手了
He handed it off before Victor tracked him down.
杀了他真是便宜他了
Wasn't enough to kill him.
这个贪心的崽子还偷了克鲁兹的手机
This greedy motherfucker stole Cruz's phone,
把我们引到他的家里
led us right to his place.
发现他正和他女人在床上
Found him in bed with her.
这蠢货还以为自己自由了
Moron thought he was home free,
正要和他女人做爱庆祝
about to have his celebration fuck.
那你他妈的把他带到这来干嘛?
Why the fuck would you bring him here?
- 嗯? - 今天是开业日
- Hmm? - It's opening night.
楼上人满为患
I got a full house upstairs.
我以为你想亲自教训教训这个狗娘养的
I thought you'd want to teach this motherfucker a lesson.
那那个女的?
And the girl?
我们要用她来逼他开口
He needed some persuasion to talk.
怎么了?
What?
我们得放了那个女的
We got to let her go.
汤米 用脑子想想
Tommy, think.
这女的有兄弟姐妹
This girl has brothers, cousins,
一些关心在乎她的人
someone who gives a fuck about her.
你把她卷进来 她家里人就会到处找她
You fuck with her, they come running, looking for her.
他们带刀或者带枪
They come with machetes or they come with guns.
泰诺人兄弟, 索尔达多族
Hermanos Tainos, Soldado Nation.
我们打交道的 或更糟 我们没交情的
People we deal with, or worse, people we don't.
和玛丽亚说再见 米格尔
Say good-bye to Maria, Miguel.
噢 米格尔
Oh, Miguel.
嘿 对不起
Hey, I'm sorry.
米格尔 求求你说了吧
Miguel, por favor.
米格尔 宝贝! 米格尔! 米格尔!
Miguel, baby! Miguel! Miguel!
回家 洗个澡
Go home, take a shower.
我会派我的人送你回去 好吗?
I'll send my man here with you, okay?
你把那些衣服给他 然后你第二天照常去上班
You give him these clothes. You go to work tomorrow
就像什么事也没发生过 如果有人问起
like nothing happened. If somebody ask you,
你就说你和米格利图分手了 明白?
you and Miguelito broke up, understand?
你从没来过这
You were never here.
好的 好的!
Si. Si!
你等她洗完澡
You stay with her till she's out of the shower,
- 然后把她衣服烧了再走 - 米格尔!
- and then burn her clothes. - Miguel!
玛丽亚 对不起!
Maria! I'm sorry!
米格尔!
Miguel!
这里 米格利图
Well, well, here we are, Miguelito.
我和你
You and me,
两个都不想呆在这的人
two men who would rather be anywhere but here.
我本来还有别的事 你呢?
I know I had other plans. How 'bout you?
我知道你有计划 米格尔
I know you had a plan, Miguel.
你不是偶然杀了负责帮我收钱的人
You didn't hit my money man by chance.
有人告诉你 去哪 杀谁
Someone told you where to go, who to hit.
我一个字也不会告诉你的
Man, I ain't gonna tell you shit.
米拉...米拉 我们把玛丽亚放了
Mira...Mira. We let Maria go.
你只要告诉我们谁指使你的
Tell me who set this up,
我也会放了你
and I'll let you go too.
我不能 我不能 我不能
I can't. I can't. I can't.
求求你 求求你 好吗?
Pl... please, man. Please, okay?
我发誓了不能说 我发誓了 噢我的天呐
I swear to God. I swear to God. Oh, God.
我们都知道会怎么样
We both know how this ends.
没人能开开心心地走出这扇大门 不是吗?
Neither one of us walks out of here a happy man, huh?
我不想背信弃义 我不想
I don't wanna rat. I don't.
- 真的吗? - 是的
- What? - Yes.
圣帕特里克夫人 你看到过老板吗?
Mrs. St. Patrick. You seen the boss?
我想给他看今晚目前入场的人数
I want to show him the numbers so far tonight.
令人难以置信
We're killing it.
没有 但你可以给我看
No, but you can show them to me.
我不知道老板会不会同意
I don't know if I'm supposed to do that.
你可以给我看
You can show them to me.
今晚棒极了 人满爆棚
We're having an amazing night. Off the charts.
你说是就是
If you say so.
他长得真帅
He's cute.
米格尔 你的问题是
Your problem is, Miguel,
你为了你的愚忠而经受不必要的痛苦
you suffer from a serious case of misplaced loyalty.
你想保护的人
The men you're protecting sent you out to steal from
让你今晚去偷一群不该惹的人
the wrong motherfuckers tonight.
或许他们高估了你 或许他们低估了我们
Either they overestimated you or they underestimated us.
但他们选择让你背黑锅 小伙伴
But they left you hanging out to dry, partner.
告诉我谁雇了你
Tell me who hired you.
然后你可以跟着我们混
And then you can come work for us.
今晚你还能回你的床上睡
Tonight, you sleep in tu cama.
你还有一次机会 米格利图
You still have a choice, Miguelito.
你选吧
如果我说了...
我的家人就会有危险
我不怕死
I'm not afraid to die.
那我也不怕杀了你
And I'm not afraid to kill you.
把这里清理干净
Clean that up.
我要这里弄得一干二净
I want the shit spotless,
就像她妈的什么都没发生过!
like it never fucking happened!
这人完全没用
This shit makes no sense.
我们今晚有十九个交货司机对吧?
We had 19 drivers delivering product tonight, right?
二十个 赛布斯奥有个单身派对
20. Sabueso caught a bachelor party.
只能在那卖
Had to stay on to deliver.
然后这狗杂种
And this motherfucker here hits Cruz
在克鲁兹带着一整天赚得钱的时候 杀了他?
when he's holding the money from all the day runs?
还有我们今晚要用的
Plus we did that brick drop tonight.
- 所有批发要用到的钱 - 是的
- The wholesale shit. - Right.
所以克鲁兹今天拿的现金
So Cruz is carrying today's cash
是他妈的我们整个组织的钱 汤米
from our whole fucking organization, Tommy.
整个组织
The whole fucking organization.
如果他晚二十分钟
If he gets here 20 minutes later,
在他房里做完买卖再到这
after he's made the drop at the house,
他们一个子也拿不到 你明白吗?
they get nothing. What does that tell you?
那混蛋跟我们的人勾结
Asshole was working with one of our people.
假如有人知道了我们的事怎么办?
What if it's someone who knows our fucking business?
泰诺人 洛克街女杀手 索尔达多族.
Tainos, Rock Street Killahz, Soldado Nation.
他们为何要恩将仇报呢?
Why would they bite the hand that feeds them?
跟我们作对 他们就没渠道了
They fuck with us, they lose their distro.
因为是人都厌恶中间人 伙计
Because everybody hates middle management, man.
也许他们想要直接跟货源接洽
Maybe they wanted to go straight to the source.
操 没人有本事直接向洛沃斯
Shit, none of these guys got the stones
挑衅
to fuck with Lobos directly.
但是 Soldados或泰诺人兄弟
Still, the Soldados or Hermanos Tainos
要想搞垮我们 就得将我们斩草除根
wanted to take us down, they'd hit
除非他们一击即中
all our people, all at once.
也就是说现在我们所有人
Which means we have to take
要撤出这条街
everybody off the street, now.
关店?
Close the store?
我们经不起第二波袭击了
We can't afford to get hit again.
如果有内鬼
If one of our people is behind this,
我们都不知道幕后黑手
we don't know who they're working with.
向谁反击
We don't know who to hit back.
我们不能
We can't stand around with our dicks
坐以
in our hands waiting on the other guy
待毙
to make his next move.
怎么了?
What's up?
我们取消圣诞活动
We're canceling Christmas.
立刻全部停止
Shut it all down, now.
买足够多的药让姑娘们亢奋
Just buy enough to keep the girls happy.
漫漫长夜呢
We got a long night ahead of us.
- 妈的 - 怎么了?
- Shit. - What?
- 我得走了 - 等等 去哪?
- I gotta go. - Wait, where you going?
- 等等 去哪?
Wait. Where you going?
老兄? 我不差钱
Dude? I'm the best man.
现在我该干嘛?
What the fuck am I supposed to do now?
四十五桌刚喝了清酒
Table 45 was drinking Wataribune Sake.
把这些放回吧台 然后
Take that back to the bar, and when you're done,
去七十二 六十八 六十四桌卖酒
flip the bottles at 72, 68, and 64.
他们都要点下一轮了
They all need to order another round.
我想他们喝酒慢了下来
I think they're slowing down.
那就让他们起身出去 上帝 外面大把人
Then get them up and out, holly... we got people outside
想进来消费呢 快去
who want to give us their money. Go.
噢 老天 真尽兴
Oh, my God, I had so much fun.
我也是 姑凉
I know, me too, girl.
谢谢捧场
Thanks for coming.
没事 宝贝 电话联络
All right, babe. Call me later.
- 好的 - 好
- All right. - Okay.
- 注意安全回家 La凯莎 - 嗨 谢谢
- Get home safely, Lakeisha. - Hi. Thank you.
- 还好吧? - 没事
- Everything okay? - Yeah.
你还好吗? 招待宾客?
You good? Entertaining our guests?
现在很晚了 宝贝 我们回家吧?
It's late, baby. Why don't we go home?
我们可以单独庆祝一下
You know, we could do a little celebrating of our own.
你去拿车 送你回去后让肖恩再来找我
You take the car. Send Shawn back for me.
- 亚历克斯 - 是
- Alex. - Yeah.
请你护送我老婆出门
Can you please escort my wife to the door?
晚安 小T
Night, T.
我再转转
I'm sticking around.
现在回去吗 圣帕特里克夫人?
Going home now, Mrs. St. Patrick?
我还能去哪呢?
Where else would I go?
看到了吗 老爸?
See that, pop?
我做到了
I did it.
你儿子做到了
Your boy did it.
我到处找你
I've been looking all over for you.
每个人都没嫌疑
Everyone got clear.
没问题 没人干坏事
No problems. Nobody tried shit.
一直忙忙碌碌 打拼工作
All the hustling, all the work.
从一开始为布雷兹和卡南管理堂口
From working the corner for Breeze and Kanan.
到如今
It brought us here.
你明白的 汤米 像我们这样长大的傻瓜
You know, for two knuckleheads that grew up like us, Tommy,
能在城里立足 不是一件容易的事
to make it in the city, man, ain't no small shit.
关店前我们损失了两十万
We lost 200k tonight, before we closed the store.
加上由此引发的损失
Plus whatever we lost since.
卖酒水来弥补损失吗?
We make up for that selling drinks?
钱不是真正的问题所在
The money ain't the real problem.
靠 这不是问题
Fuck that, it's not the real problem.
不 真正的问题是...我们要找出
No, the real problem... we need to find out
幕后黑手
who the fuck is behind this.
今晚米格尔为了保护他们而死
Miguel died tonight to protect them.
我们要找到答案
We need answers.
尽快
Quick.
尤其是告诉洛沃斯我们遭袭后
Especially after we tell Lobos we got hit.
妈的 我说我们不要告诉他吧
Shit, I say we don't tell him.
他无须知道此事
He ain't gotta know about this.
我们付钱给他
We pay him,
- 不就没事了 - 不
- get the fuck out of there. - Nah.
我们得预先就解除麻烦
We gotta get out in front of it, man.
我们只为他效劳六个月
Only six months we're working for him.
没有根基
We got no history built.
洛沃斯察觉此事后 发现我们瞒报?
Lobos finds out about this, and we ain't say shit?
不管怎么说是我们的责任 我们把
It's our ass anyway. We got his product sitting
他的货放在集装箱
in a goddamn shipping container
一分一秒钱都在流失
losing money by the minute.
- 你老妈? - 是啊
- Your mom? - Yeah.
她可能又睡不着了
She probably can't fucking sleep again.
我只是说洛沃斯到处惹事
I'm just saying, Lobos sets fire to people.
伙计 那人跟他妹妹搞在一起
That guy was fucking his sister, man.
我们要给他他的那份钱...现金
We gotta give him his money... cash.
没错 我有一半 但在我妈那
Yeah. I got half. But it's out at my mother's.
我明天带过来
I'll bring it tomorrow.
嗨 我听到反馈了 E.O.那边那家伙?
Hey, I heard back from drift. That guy over in E.O.?
他想下周和我们接头
He wants to get up with us next week.
谈论从我们这买进
Talked about buying from us.
我们得拖住泽西那边
Nah, we gotta hold off on Jersey.
直道我们查出怎么回事
Not till we find out what the fuck's going on.
不要火中取栗
Can't expand under fire.
嗨
Hey,
提一句 你找了群身材很正的妞
You got some fine-ass-looking girls
送酒水
serving drinks in there, by the way.
其中一位...红发 高挑
There was this one... red hair, tall.
敢问芳名?
What's her name?
噢 是 是 是 是啊 是啊
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
- 对啊 - 她的名字是...
- Yeah. - Her name is...
别染指货物 臭小子
Don't touch the merchandise, motherfucker.
别碰...好吧
Don't touch the... okay.
你会对红发念念不忘?
You ever gonna get over that red hair shit?
可能会
Probably not.
什么时候回来的?
When did you get home?
很晚了
Late.
我可以让你放松下来...
You know, I could help you relax...
如果你放手于我
If you let me.
噢 别 塔什
Oh, come on, Tash.
让我来
Let me.
我不能 拜托了
I can't. Please.
求你了 大哥
Please, man. Please.
我不怕死
I'm not afraid to die.
而我也不介意杀了你
And I'm not afraid to kill you.
- 来嘛 - 我得走了
- Come here. - I gotta go.
什么?
What?
你去哪?
Where you going?
雷娜 你在干嘛?
Raina, what are you doing?
她在排练 妈妈
She's rehearsing, mom.
低年级的学校剧试音会
The auditions for the lower school
将在一个月后 我想好好准备
play in a month, and I want to be prepared.
我说的是你的衣服
I'm talking about your outfit.
宝贝 这一点都不衬你身材
It's not flattering in your shape, baby.
我给你买的那件裙子呢?
How about that nice dress I bought you?
没人穿裙子去学校 外婆
Nobody wears dresses to school, big mama.
爸爸的乖女儿
Daddy's little girly.
早 埃斯特尔
Morning, Estelle.
早上好
Good morning.
我们要举办茶花会
We're gonna have a tea party
堆城堡
and play with the castle.
来吧
Come on.
- 过来和外婆坐 - 洛沃斯.
- Sit up here with grandma. - Lobos.
还见面吗?
克拉罗
Claro.
我周二得交西班牙语作业
So I got Spanish homework due Tuesday.
- 依我看老爸就可以搞定? - 不
- Think dad could hook it up? - No.
孩子 你得自己做作业
You have to do your own work, boy.
不管怎么说他怎么会西班牙语的?
How does he know Spanish anyway?
是啊 塔莎 他怎么懂西班牙语的?
Yeah, Tasha. How does he know Spanish?
我不知道
I don't know.
在我们认识前 他就学过
He learned before we met.
早上好 圣帕特里克夫人
Morning, Mrs. St. Patrick.
- 早上好 肖恩 - 还好吧 雷娜?
- Hey, Shawn. - What's up, Reina?
塔里克 近来可好 少年?
Ah, Tariq, what's up, boy?
我们什么时候去打球 肖恩?
When we gonna hoop, Shawn?
我都求你好久了
I've been begging you forever.
孩子 放过他吧
Boy, leave him alone.
塔里克 他很忙的
Tariq, he's busy.
还有大事要做
Got a big job now.
你吃早饭吗?
You want some breakfast?
桌子上吃的足够
There's more than enough to go around.
- 随便拿 - 哦
- Go ahead. - Oh.
快来 看这个 是你的吸管杯
Come on, here. Here's your sippy.
- 是你的吸管杯 - 真棒
- Here's your sippy. - Good girl.
肖恩
Shawn.
- 儿子 - 什么事 老爸?
- Son. - What's up, dad?
上次的历史报告怎么样? 晚点儿读给我听?
How's that history report? Give me a read later?
- 好主意 - 好的
- Sounds good. - All right.
- 一天好心情哦 - 你也是
- Have a good day. - You too.
- 好运 - 好的
- Good luck, okay? - Okay.
爸爸 我爱您
Daddy loves you.
- 再见 - 再见宝贝儿
- Bye. - Bye, baby.
好的
Good.
再吃些 好吗?
Keep working on it, okay?
代我向你妈妈问好
Tell your moms I said hello.
她身体越来越差了 你知道的
She's getting worse, you know.
我不能一天都在外面
I can't be out there all the time.
洛沃斯?
Lobos?
最好别他妈的再改时间了
Better not be changing the fucking time again.
说起来 我又在想
By the way, I'm rethinking
你提议 告诉洛沃斯我们被袭击了的事儿
this whole "tell Lobos we got hit" idea of yours.
坎托斯打来的
It's Kantos.
瞧瞧他想干什么
Let's see what he wants.
怎么了?
What's up?
你知道西蒙・斯特恩吗?
You recognize the name Simon stern?
当然
Yeah.
那家伙开赌场 出版社 糖浆厂
The cat that owns parlay, verbatim, syrup.
是啊 而且 还有五家俱乐部
Yeah, plus, like, five other clubs.
他是纽约最大夜店投资者之一
He's one of the biggest nightlife investors in New York.
他公司打电话来了
His office called.
Stern 告诉《第六页》要刊登实情
Stern told the page six to write up about truth.
想找地方和我聊聊
Wants to sit down.
我这里还有烂摊子要收拾
I got a lot of shit on my plate at the moment.
咱们晚点再说
We'll talk later.
这是件大事
It's a big deal.
他只找大佬们谈生意
He only talks to the major guys.
听着 有Stern当我们的靠山
Look, with Stern behind us,
明年年底 我们就可以在迈阿密和维加斯
we can open up clubs in Miami and Vegas
开几家夜店
end of next year.
我会给你回电话的 伙计
I'll call you back, man.
他有什么问题?
What's his problem now?
不过呢 别管他
You know what, never mind.
我们有正事儿要办
We got real shit to do.
幽灵 汤米 很高兴再次见到你们
Ghost, Tommy. Good to see you again.
我的钱带来了吗?
You have my money, of course?
一 二 三 四 五 六...
Uno, dos, tres, cuatro, cinco, seis...
别数出声
难道你以为自己还是中学生吗?
佩德罗
佩德罗换你来数
全都在这里 所有的
It's all there. Todo.
所有的
Todo.
佩德罗
Pedro.
可以了
Orale.
现在把生意上的事儿解决了
Now that the business is out of the way,
我们可以尽情吃喝玩乐 好吗?
we can eat and enjoy ourselves, eh?
最近怎么样?
How are things?
马马虎虎虎
Just fine.
有些事得和你说
Something you need to know.
什么事?
Hmm?
我们昨晚被袭击了
We got hit last night.
我听说了
So I heard.
- 你们抓住那人了吗? - 抓住了
- Did you catch this man? - We got him.
他知道袭击的时间 地点和对象
He knew who to hit, where and when.
所以在知道是谁指使他之前 敌暗我明
So until we know how he got his information, we're exposed.
- 看来他不肯招咯? - 真是不识时务
- Oh, so he didn't talk? - Unfortunately for him.
你也是
Unfortunately for you.
你把你的人从街上撤走了
You took your men off the street.
没办法 必须撤走
Had to. No choice.
你每小时损失近两万五千美元
You're losing about $25,000 an hour.
还好你没有让这些事
It's good to see that you knew enough
影响我们保护费金额
not to let it affect our pay schedule.
六个月前我聘用你当我的纽约代理商时
When I hired you six months ago to be my New York distributor,
你向我保证提供高水准服务
you guaranteed me a certain level of professionalism.
你告诉我那些公司 像国王团啊
You told me that the kings,
敢死党啊 还有DDP...
the bloods, the DDP...
都不值得我浪费时间
that none of them were worth my time.
我相信你说的
I believe the exact words were,
他们不过是小喽罗 我们才是生意人
"They're gangs. And we're a business."
你还告诉我只有你可以保证
You also told me that only you could guarantee me
24小时不间断的
a safe and secure pipeline
- 安全可靠渠道 - 拜托 洛沃斯
- with no interruptions. - Come on, Lobos.
你知道这个行业 是没有保证的
You know in this business, there's no guarantees.
我们已经有应对计划了
We have a plan to fix this situation.
那你们没有时间吃中午饭了 下午好 先生们
Then you don't have time for lunch. Good afternoon, gentlemen.
鬼魂
我发现了
你的名声可高于你的本事
你的大名在外面很有震慑力
如果你能控制住这局面
终有一天你也会有自己的垄断联盟 明白吗?
是
Si.
而你的人却在外面冒险
你一年做两三天生意
如果你不办事 我就换别的公司 到时你对我还有什么用?
我们会搞定的
对 你能行
再见 老板
再见 幽灵
给飞行员打电话
我们今晚不走了
我去找鲁伊斯
I'll go see Ruiz.
你负责去问阿尼巴尔和罗拉 好吗?
You get Anibal and Rolla, deal?
好的
Yeah.
晚上见
See you tonight.
- 小心点 - 你也是 混蛋
- And watch your back. - You too, motherfucker.
都搞好了吗? 包括后备箱?
Full detail, right? Even the trunk?
- 特别密封了后备箱 - 很好
- Especially the trunk. - Good.
我讨厌血腥味
I hate the smell of blood.
汤米
幽灵在哪儿?
他向您问好
He sends his regards.
你会玩牌吗?
You play Dominoes?
这不是社交见面 阿尼巴尔
This is not a social visit, Anibal.
我们昨晚都被袭击了
We got hit last night.
我的错 我之前没听到什么消息
My bad, I ain't hear that.
一点风声都没有?
Not a word?
一点都没有
Nada.
好吧 干的那么大一票
Yeah, well, a score like that
总有人会提前吹牛的
somebody will brag about.
你肯定知道什么的
You hear something,
五万块
50 stacks.
你要把他活着带来 给你七万五
75 if you bring him to us alive.
他对你们那么重要吗?
Means that much to you?
如果他是你的人 你可以亲自杀了他
If it's one of your men, you can kill him yourself.
我们只要看着就行
We just want to watch.
如果我知道是谁干的 我早就杀了他们了
If I knew who ordered it, yeah, they'd be dead already.
什么
我们也遭袭了
我的损失和你的一样多 哥们
My money guy, same as yours.
他们打死了我手下 天使
They shot my boy, angel.
直穿后脑
in the back of the head.
- 还有个未出生的孩子 - 太操蛋了
- Had a baby on the way. - That's fucked up.
听着 我知道 你跟着其它帮派
Look. I know, okay, you work with other crews.
我们可能都会因此而死
你得事情变得更糟前制止它
You have to stop this before it goes any further.
我能借你几个人保护你
I could lend you men, extra protection.
不行 如果他们知道我们并肩作战
Nah, if they know we ride
我就会失去泰诺人和洛克街的信任
together, I lose trust of the tainos and rock street.
无论如何别相信他们
汤米和我是中立的
Tommy and I are neutral.
你知道的 爸爸
Tu sabes eso, papa.
拜托
Come on.
好吧
Bueno.
说不定我们现在还能再干点什么
Maybe there's something else that we could work out.
这是冠军 汤米叔叔
It's the lead, uncle Tommy.
如果是我夺冠的话 这绝对是件大新闻
If I get it, it'll be like a huge deal.
因为我才五年级
'Cause I'm only in the fifth grade.
我敢肯定 你唱的歌一定是
I'm sure you got the best singing voice
最好听的 小丫头
in the whole place, baby girl.
你什么时候才能不叫我小丫头啊?
When are you gonna stop calling me that?
我不是小孩了 茉莉才是
I'm not the baby anymore. Jasmine is.
我眼看着你出生
I was there when you were born.
你在我心里永远都是小丫头
You'll always be baby girl to me.
在我们心里都是
To all of us.
- 小丫头 - 汤米再吃些鸡肉
- Baby girl. - Tommy, have some more chicken.
嗯嗯 哦 嗯嗯 谢谢啦 T
Mmm, oh. Mmm. Thanks, T.
如果你要是遇到一个会做饭的姑娘
You know, if you meet a girl who can cook,
我猜我们就再见不到你了
I bet we'd never see you again.
不可能 绝对不会的
No way that'll ever happen.
我会回来 去学校接塔里克
I gotta come over here and school Tariq in Call of Duty.
- 好啊好啊 汤米叔叔 - 好的
- Yeah, right, uncle Tommy. - Yeah, right.
因为你知道你本不该玩
because you know you're not supposed to be
这些游戏的
playing those games anyway.
哦 都是我不好
Oh, my bad.
给我掌上明珠的星星
Stars for my little star.
继续努力你的试音吧
Keep working hard on that audition.
嘿
Hey.
等等 爸爸 这是真钻石吗?
Wait, daddy. Are these real diamonds?
你说呢?
What you think, huh?
如果你总这样 你会把她惯坏的
If you keep this up, you're gonna spoil her rotten.
我送你礼物的时候你咋不说呢
And you don't complain when I do it to you.
给我准备一个盘子 好吗?
Fix me a plate, okay?
汤米和我要在办公室谈事情
Tommy and I are gonna talk in the office.
我们有活儿干了
We got work to do.
让我看看这些钻石 小宝贝儿
Let me see them diamonds, baby girl.
索尔达多族也遭劫了
Soldado Nation got hit too.
不会吧
No shit.
鲁伊斯通过他佛罗里达州那边的关系
Ruiz got a full shipment of weapons
上周得到了一船的武器
from his c connect last week.
全面动员我们的司机直到把事情解决
Our drivers can have full use till the shit blows over
直到抓到那个王八蛋
or until we catch the motherfucker.
他提出派他们的人和我们一起
He offered to have his people ride with ours.
- 去他妈的吧 - 去他妈的吧
- Fuck that. - Fuck that.
尽管枪杆子底下出政权
The guns, though, that could work.
我知道你不喜欢这种方式
I know you don't like it.
警察禁止司机
Police stop a driver
运输消遣性货物及现金
carrying recreational weight and some cash,
汤米 不能掉以轻心
Tommy, that's one thing.
车里有枪 你要看动机
But a gun in the car,you're looking at intent
及武器的掌管
to distribute, plus the weapons charge.
卡南等到了什么...十五年牢狱之灾?
Kanan got what... 15 years?
你有更好的主意吗?
You got a better idea?
因为我们要开店不然洛沃斯就会撇下我们
because we gotta open up the store or Lobos will move on.
更不用说我们的人没活儿干了
Not to mention our people off the clock,
我们的客户都会另辟蹊径
and our customers will find new places to cop.
假使说我们找到了那个混蛋
Let's say we find the motherfucker.
而他是阿尼巴尔的人
And it is one of Anibal's people
或者是洛克街女杀手或者爱谁谁
or Rock Street Killahz or whoever.
- 那又怎样? - 那我们就开始吧
- Then what? - Then it's on.
那我们就拿下他妈的整个团伙
Then we take down the whole fucking crew.
我们向他们展示 向所有人展示
We show them. We show everybody.
你们不能像以前那样跟我得瑟
You can't fuck with us, like the old days
在卡南成为局内人之前
before Kanan went inside.
我们那时太年轻 摇摆不定
We were young then. Mobile.
现在我有太他妈多事忙了
I got too much shit going on now
太多事要隐瞒
to go into hiding.
孩子 夜总会...
The kids, the club...
等一下 所以现在夜总会迫使我们
oh, wait, so now the club dictates
干点儿正经买卖
what we do with the real business
而不是旁门左道?
instead of the other way around?
我们开这个自助洗衣店来洗钱
And we opened up the laundromats to clean the money.
我觉得挺好的
I was fine with that.
但是你却说"我们开个夜店
But then you said, "let's open up a nightclub.
这样我们能藏更多"
So we can hide even more."
于是我就同意了...藏钱
So I agreed... to hide the money.
句号
Period.
要是不仅如此呢 伙计?
What if there could be more than that though, man?
要是这就是我们的退休计划呢?
What if it's our retirement plan?
你的意思是我们不小了 走合法道路
You mean we grow up, go legit,
快乐终老?
live happily ever after?
抱歉...
I'm sor...
我们一直在一起拼搏忙碌
We've been hustling together our whole lives.
我热爱我们干的这行 你也是
I love this shit and so do you.
全神贯注
Focus up.
我说我们接受鲁伊斯的提案
I say we take Ruiz up on his offer.
我们把兄弟们布置回大街小巷
We put the boys back on the street,
谁敢捣乱
and if anyone steps,
他们就会把这王八蛋揪出来
they light that motherfucker up.
同意不?
Agreed?
好
Yeah.
今晚我出去到鲁伊斯那拿枪
We'll go out and get the guns from Ruiz tonight.
我去布置
I'll set it up.
我不跟你去了 你带上胡里奥
Go without me. Take Julio.
我要去夜总会办点儿别的事
I gotta handle a few things at the club.
你想要一个长期洗钱的地方
You want a place to clean our money long-term,
你得保证她营业 对吧?
it's gotta stay open, right?
这才是我说的一起他妈的奋斗
Now that's the motherfucking hustler I know talking.
夜总会见
I'll see you at the club later.
我走了
I'm going now.
今晚确保所有事都搞定
Gotta make sure everything's settled for tonight.
那个新来的白人不能做吗?
Can't that new white boy do that?
你给他开的不少
You pay him enough.
这是生意 亲爱的
It's a business, baby.
- 要全程警惕 - 我也是
- It needs attention 24/7. - So do I.
幽灵 怎么了?
Ghost, what's up?
你和汤米关着门
You and Tommy behind closed doors,
你一直在夜总会转悠
you running around with this club.
我们没事吧?
We okay?
我们认识时
When we met,
你认为我会变成什么样的人?
who'd you think I was gonna be?
嗯?
Hmm?
全纽约最他妈大的
The biggest goddamn drug dealer
毒枭
in New York City.
你从没想过更多吗?
You never thought about more?
什么更多?
What more?
你说的夜总会就是更多吗?
You talking about the club as more?
我看见了你昨晚赚的钱
I saw the money you made last night.
那不是更多 是至少
That's not more, it's less.
你很擅长你所做的事
You are the best at what you do.
我们什么都有
We have everything.
我就想要这样
I just want it to stay this way.
怎么了?
What?
今晚当你进入夜总会时
When you come to the club tonight,
你需要看起来像拥有这个地方
you need to look like you own the place,
而不是像试图要免费进去
not like you trying to get in for free.
穿那件上个月我给你的紫色裙子
Wear that purple dress I got you last month.
但是 亲爱的 我喜欢这件
But, baby, I like this dress.
我派肖恩回来 给你时间换衣服
I'll send Shawn back, give you time to change.
你看见我老公没?
Have you seen my husband?
有人看见老板了吗?
Anybody got eyes on the boss?
老板现在在准备DJ
The boss is prepping the DJ now.
我带你上楼
I'll take you upstairs.
我知道哪儿能让他快点儿见到我
I know where he'll get to me a little sooner.
嘿
Hey.
怎么了?
What's up?
DJ带来了后补舞者
The DJ brought backup dancers
这些舞者不在合同里
who are not in the contract.
好 我们手头有特别出色的吗?
Well, we got extra spotlights on hand?
我们能找到
We could find them.
找人给他们安排食宿
Have the guys put them up.
老板 你去哪?
Boss, where you going?
安琪
Angie.
- 杰米? - 安吉拉・巴尔德斯.
- Jamie? - Angela Valdes.
我们多久没见面了?
How long has it been?
我不知道
I don't know.
差不多...
Almost...
天呀 十八年了
Jesus, 18 years.
你还是老样子
You look the same.
算了吧 这证明我们都老了
Well, that's proof we've gotten older.
你度数涨了吧
Your eyesight's going.
我眼神儿老好了
My eyes work just fine.
忙啥呢?
What have you been doing?
这十八年来?
For 18 years?
不确定 比较简短
Not sure there's a short answer.
高中 大学 法学院...
Choate, college, law school...
法学院?
law school?
- 好呀 不错嘛 - 别提了
- Okay, big-time. - Stop it.
我一如既往还是那个简单的女孩
I'm still the same "round the way" girl I always was.
和以前一样? 不见得吧
Same girl, huh? Not exactly.
我不记得这件裙子了
I don't remember that dress.
是呀 我也不记得这西装了 土豪
Well, I don't remember that suit either, uptown.
你在忙什么呢 杰米?
What have you been up to, Jamie?
这些年你一直干嘛呢?
What have you been doing all these years?
老板 新来的DJ要开始了
Boss, the new DJ's gonna start.
等等 他刚才叫你问"老板"?
Wait, did he just call you "boss"?
这地方是我的
I own this place.
坎托斯说他现在就要和谈谈
Kantos said he needs to talk to you now.
好的
All right.
抱歉 我得...
Sorry, I gotta...
你得管理你的夜总会
You got a nightclub to run.
我明白
I get it.
很高兴见到你
it was good to see you.
我也是
You too.
把你的电话号码给我
You know what, give me your number.
这次我不会这么容易让你逃跑的
I ain't gonna let you get away that easy.
我会打给你的
I'll call you.
好
Okay.
圣帕特里克夫人 你现在就要走了吗?
Mrs. St. Patrick, you're not leaving, are you?
新的DJ马上就要开始了
The new DJ starts in a few minutes,
老大一定也很想看到你
and I'm sure the boss wants you to be here.
肖恩 到门口接我
Shawn, meet me out front.
我准备走了
I'm leaving.
都准备好了吗?
对 这次是个大生意
Yeah, a big shipment this time.
都是清白的
好的
Bueno.
这些都是免费送的吗?
We're really giving this away for free?
只有这一次
This time.
我们到那儿之后 你待在车里
When we get there, you stay in the car.
我和庞曹去完成交易
Me and Poncho will handle the drop.
我已经约好了跟那个家伙见面
I set up the meeting with the guy you asked.
- 很好 - 爸爸
- Good. - Papi.
明天放学后我能跟罗西奥和拉腊去看电影吗?
晚饭前回来 我要带你去你妈妈那 知道吗?
Be home by dinner, so I can take you to your mom's, okay?
知道了
Okay.
赶快进屋 以免感冒
知道了 爸爸
Okay, pa.
威姆诺斯 走吧 我们要迟到了
Vamonos. Let's go, we're late.
胡里奥有没有让他们检查一下这些枪?
Julio tell them to check the guns?
我一开始就跟他说了
First thing I said to him.
这些人根本不知道自己在为谁卖命 不是吗?
Think it bothers them they don't know who they're working for?
你以为汉堡王的煎炸厨师
You think the fry cook at burger king
认识他们的总裁吗?
knows the fucking ceo?
老板进来店里要番茄酱的时候
They wouldn't know that motherfucker
他们都不会认出来
if he walked in and asked for extra ketchup.
别忘了
Don't forget.
让克鲁兹第一个被突袭的人
One of these people might be the reason
可能就在这些人中间
Cruz got jumped in the first place.
知道 希望这次这个家伙是个怕死鬼
Yeah, well, let's hope he or she is afraid to get shot.
我们马上就会知道了
We'll know soon enough.
我们的士兵们都已经有装备了
Our soldiers are strapped now.
我们也应该有
We should be too.
事情已经这样了
All this shit going on,
我再让你这样手无寸铁地到处溜达
how am I gonna explain to Tasha
到时候我怎么跟塔莎解释啊?
I let you run around with no piece?
把他们都叫出去吧
Let's get 'em out on the street.
是时候让我们的厨师做甜甜圈了
Time to make the doughnuts.
18年后也不错
Not bad for 18 years later.
格雷格
Greg.
你好 睡美人
Hey, sleepyhead.
你今天早上怎么没有一起跑步
You missed our run this morning.
你没过来 也没有接电话
When you didn't show up and you didn't answer your cell,
我以为你出什么事了
I thought maybe something was wrong.
该死
Shit.
抱歉
Sorry.
我来的时候你在洗澡
Got here and you were in the shower,
我就自己找早餐吃了
so I thought I'd grab breakfast.
格雷格 我记得我说过给你钥匙是为了应付紧急状况
Greg, I thought we said the key was just for emergencies.
这就是紧急情况啊
Which this could've been.
这让我感觉有点...
This just feels a little...
你没有必要时时刻刻看着我
You don't need to check on me.
别这样 安吉拉 我想大部分女人
Come on, Angela, I think most women
知道有人担心自己都会很开心的
would be happy to know that someone's looking out for them.
你说得对 抱歉
You're right. I'm sorry.
我只是被你吓了一跳
You just startled me is all.
谢谢你
Thank you.
我得走了
I gotta go.
待会儿见
See you later.
安吉拉・巴尔德斯昨天晚上到俱乐部来了
Angela Valdes came into the club last night.
高中的那个?
From high school?
- 哇哦 那得多久了... - 18年了
- Wow. What's that... - 18 years.
她看起来怎么样?
How'd she look?
有那么好吗?
That good, huh?
她结婚了没 有孩子吗?
She married now, she got kids?
没戴戒指 也没有谈到孩子
No ring, didn't say nothing about kids.
那你有没有跟她谈起你的孩子?
You tell her about yours?
我们只聊了一会儿
Well, we didn't talk that long.
- 该死 - 你那是什么意思?
- Oh, shit. - What's that supposed to mean?
我的意思是你到底在想什么?
What that means is what are you thinking about doing?
那女的离开的时候 她就已经把你给甩了
When that girl moved away, she seriously fucked you up.
- 我看得很明白 记得吗? - 哦 拜托
- I was there, remember? - Aw, come on.
那已经很久之前的事了
That was a long time ago.
塔莎是个好女人 兄弟
Well, Tasha's a good woman, man.
你之前从来没有乱搞过
You ain't never fucked around on her before.
现在怎么会想起来高中的女朋友了
Why do you want to go sniffing around pussy from high school?
汤米 首先 我真是不敢相信
Tommy, first of all, I can't believe
不要乱搞这种话会从你的嘴里出来
you starting some shit about monogamy.
你自己都不知道跟多少个女人发生关系了
You got more bitches than a goddamn pound,
第二 我知道我跟塔莎什么问题都没有
but second, I know me and Tasha got a good thing.
我也没有想过要搞砸我们的婚姻
I'm not trying to fuck that up.
只是这让我想起了
It's just got me thinking, you know,
当初错过的一些东西
about the road not traveled, that's all.
"错过的东西"?
"The road not traveled"?
你已经是一个富有的成功人士
You are a rich, successful motherfucker.
你还有什么想要的?
What more do you want?
我想知道她现在变成什么样了
I want to see how Angela turned out.
你现在已经知道了
No, you already saw how she turned out.
其他的一切都只是你试图治愈幼年的伤痛
Anything else is just you trying to heal wounds from childhood.
我看你别再去看尔骗子菲尔医生了
You gotta stop watching that Dr. Philshit.
他真是什么事都知道
That man knows what he's talking about.
闭嘴 停车
Shut up. Sit down.
你才闭嘴
You shut up.
你闭嘴
No, shut up.
再见 混蛋
So long, motherfucker.
你都没有问过我那天晚上的事
You didn't ask about that thing we did the other night.
你按我说的处理干净了吗?
You clean it up like I said?
那我就没什么好问的了
Then there ain't nothing to ask about.
- 干嘛 你以为我忘了? - 是啊
- What, you think I forgot? - Yeah, I do.
赶紧滚吧
Get the fuck out of here.
这个能借我吗?
Can I borrow this?
不行 那是新的
No way, girl. That's new.
但是Gucci的那件可以给你
But the Gucci, you can have that.
天呐 你简直要被幽灵宠坏了
Damn, girl. Ghost keeps you laced.
我不管这么多
Yo, I don't care.
你有什么不要的
I'll take your hand-me-downs
全部扔给我好了
as long as you're giving them out.
这才是真正的幸福生活啊
So this is what happily ever after looks like.
你真是中大奖了
You hit the lottery, girl.
黑人结婚可不是这样
Niggas ain't getting married like that,
而且一定也不是富有的黑人
and certainly not rich niggas.
我认识他的时候他也是个穷光蛋
He wasn't rich when I met him.
你知道吗 凯莎
You know, Keisha,
有衣服和包包当然很好
clothes and bags are nice,
但幽灵有些事情你也不知道
but there are some things about ghost you can't see.
你跟我就不用装了 塔莎
You don't gotta play modest with me, Tasha.
我没有
I'm not playing modest.
我不会嫉妒死的
I'm not gonna die of jealousy over here,
更不用说你还有这么多靴子
especially if you're through with these boots.
等一下 你穿多大码的鞋子?
Hold up, what size you wear again?
欧洲的这些鞋码我一直搞不懂
You know I don't get all this European shit.
嗨 亲爱的
Hey, baby.
你跟闺蜜出去逛街了吗?
You out shopping with Lakeisha yet?
- 我们还在家 - 很好
- We're still at the house. - Good.
我在家里烤箱里放了个东西 你帮我保管一下
I got something in the oven I need you to take care of.
塔莎 你听到没?
Tasha, you heard me?
我要你在它被烧成灰之前把它拿出来
I need you to take it out before it burns.
好 我知道了
Yes, I'm on it.
好
Yeah.
谢谢你 亲爱的
Thank you, baby.
好 晚上见
Okay, I'll see you tonight.
什么事?
What was that?
他给我留了些钱去购物
He left me some extra money to go shopping.
我现在去拿 马上回来
I'll just go get it. I'll be right back.
现在你知道我说的什么意思吧?
You see what I mean?
你真是中大奖了
You hit the motherfucking lottery.
妈的
Damn.
- 你好? - 安吉拉
- Hello? - Angela.
- 杰米? - 你没想到我会打过来吧?
- Jamie? - You surprised I called?
我说过这一次不会让你逃跑了
I told you I wasn't gonna let you get away again,
我是认真的
and I meant it.
- 一起吃午饭吧 - 不行
- Come have lunch with me. - I can't.
我今天要在全体同僚面前做一个报告
I have a presentation in front of my whole office today.
是啊 我知道你的
Yeah, and if I know you,
你都学那破玩意好几周了
you've been studying on that shit for weeks.
来吧 美女 你总要吃饭吧
Come on, girl. You gotta eat.
在哪?
Where?
你确定是这个地方吗?
是 他的手下说他们会来这里
再弄错你可承担不起了 哈维尔 其实你很幸运还有其他天赋
打扰一下
你就是卡洛斯 "摇摆"鲁伊斯?
费利佩・洛沃斯
我以为是做梦呢
你说你跟你现在的经销商出了点问题?
他没跟我说的那么可靠
于是你找波多黎各人?
你是我知道的这行中的首位墨西哥人 恕我冒犯来访
我和黑人做生意
I do business with niggers.
至少我们说同一种语言
我不管你是什么人 我只想赚钱
好吧
Bueno.
那我们谈谈生意
好吧
Bueno.
纽约大不一样了啊
New York's so different now.
城市自行车 时代广场上没有了汽车
Citi bikes, no cars in Times Square.
白人住在富人区
White people living uptown.
你没离开多久
You been gone a minute.
你终于有自己的夜店了
You finally got your nightclub.
你爸爸要是在一定会为你骄傲的
Your dad would've been proud.
我还和你说我爸的夜店了?
I told you about my father's nightclub?
在咱俩认识之前他的店就没了
He lost the place before we met.
我不记得我和你说过
I didn't remember I told you that.
我们那时候无话不说
I think we told each other everything back then.
我们最后一次吃午饭的时候 我很确定
The last time we had lunch, I'm pretty sure
那没有桌布
there was no linen tablecloths.
我也不记得有椅子
I don't think we had chairs.
我们在雷的餐厅柜台上拿吃的
We grabbed a slice at the counter at Ray's on Sutphin.
你一直在给你的可乐续杯
You kept refilling your coke.
经理用邪恶的表情看着你
The manager was giving you that evil-ass look.
你依然不为所动
You kept going.
那牌子写着 "免费续杯"
The sign said, "free refills."
我当时想让你多待会
I was trying to get you to stay longer.
我差点就误了我的火车
I almost missed my train.
那正是我的用意
That was the idea.
乔特是难得一遇的机遇
Choate was the opportunity of a lifetime.
但那不代表离开很容易
But that doesn't mean it was easy to go.
杰米 对不起
Jamie, I'm sorry.
对不起我当时那样离开
I'm sorry I left the way I did.
你父母逼你走的
Your parents made you go.
但我也没反抗他们
But I didn't fight them.
你说你圣诞节会回来
You said you'd be back for Christmas.
我走之后我家就搬到了Sunnyside
My family moved to Sunnyside after I left.
我还住在原来的地方
I had the same number.
但你就这么...
But you were just...
走了
Gone.
后来我父亲去世了
And then when my pops died,
我当时想 至少
I thought then, at least,
你会联系我
you would reach out.
我当时应该陪你的
I should've been there for you.
但我知道如果我打电话给你
But I just knew that if I called,
如果我听见你的声音
if I heard your voice,
我就会回来
I would go back.
我会为你放下一切
I would've dropped everything for you.
我父母所有的努力
Everything my parents worked for,
我所有的努力...
everything I'd worked for...
所以我做出了选择
So I made a choice.
我不会叫你回来
I wouldn't have asked you to come back.
你不属于那里
You didn't belong in the hood.
你也是
Neither did you.
不过现在我们都离开那里了
But now we're both out,
就像我们一直以来打算的那样
just like we always planned.
确切地说不是我们打算的那样
Not exactly how we planned.
- 哦 该死 - 怎么了?
- Oh, shit. - What?
- 我该走了 - 现在?
- I gotta go. - Now?
我得回办公室了
I gotta get back to the office.
- 好吧 - 谢谢你请我吃午饭
- All right. - Thanks for lunch.
嗯
Mm-hmm. Mmm.
你还记得我教你的西班牙语吗?
一点点
拜
Bye.
我们什么时候还能再出来?
When can we do this again?
我会给你打电话
I'll call you.
先别填总数
Don't fill out the total.
为什么不?
Why not?
我要在银行里核对你的总数
I'm gonna confirm your count at the bank.
我来拿着那个
I'll take that.
我所管理的所有俱乐部 都是我负责存钱
Every club I've ever managed, I always do the deposit.
凡事都有第一次 存款单
There's a first time for everything. Deposit slip.
我已经签字了 要张新的么
I already signed it. Want a fresh one?
我确定你这张没问题
Nah, I'm sure yours will turn out fine.
听着 我们雇你是因为你有关系
Look, we hired you for your contacts,
而不是因为你的声誉
not your reputation.
嘿 关于这事...
Hey, about that...
老板从来都不告诉我你是怎么知道的
boss never told me how you found out about that.
不要问我是怎么知道的
None of your fucking business how we know.
只要你给我们工作 事就这样
As long as you work for us, this is how it goes.
我们之间没问题了吧?
We don't have a problem, do we?
没有
No, we don't.
正打算派个搜查组去找你
Was just about to send out a search party for you.
- 你从来都不迟到啊 - 我知道
- You're never late. - I know.
对不起 午饭吃太久了
Sorry. Lunch ran long.
弗兰基 我知道你帮我担了风险
Frankie, I know you went out on a limb for me.
我不会搞砸的
I'm not gonna blow it.
你要是搞砸 我们都惨了
If you do, it's both our asses.
恭喜你升职 巴尔德斯
Congrats on the promotion, Valdes.
谢谢你 萨克斯
Thanks, Saxe.
-你现在管这事了? - 刚被分过来
- You're on this now? - Just got assigned.
如果我请求再分配 他们会问原因
If I request reassignment, they're gonna ask why.
我是弗朗西斯卡・拉瓦罗
I'm Francesca Lavarro,
刑事部门主管
chief of criminal division
还有我的副主管 美国陆军协会 安吉拉・巴尔德斯
along with my deputy, A.U.S.A. Angela Valdes.
我会领导这项特殊任务
I'll be leading this task force.
我们的目标就是北半球
Our goal is the prosecution of one of the most notorious
最臭名昭著的毒品交易案的原告
drug traffickers in our hemisphere,
墨西哥国籍的费利佩・洛沃斯
Mexican national Felipe Lobos.
洛沃斯残忍狠毒的本性
Lobos's brutality and vicious nature
是有证可依的
are well documented.
为了保证大家的安全
For everyone's safety,
请牢记这项特殊任务是高级机密
please remember the task force is top secret.
不能有别人 包括你们的家人
And no one, not even your families,
知道这次侦查目标的名字
can know the name of the target of this investigation.
麦迪纳特工 你能否向大家介绍
Agent Medina, can you please bring everybody up to speed
洛沃斯这周在纽约的最新动态?
on Lobos's movements in New York this week?
洛沃斯这周二空降蒂特波罗机场
Lobos landed at Teterboro airport on Tuesday.
一年一度 他来纽约
Once a year, he comes to New York
见他的庄家和他的美国律师
to meet with his banker and his American attorneys.
现在 他都见完了 但是我发现还有第三个
Now, he did make those meetings, but I followed him to a third,
和他的人...卡洛斯比沃拉鲁伊斯见面
to meet this man... Carlos "Vibora" Ruiz.
索尔达多族黑帮在本地的头头
Leader of the due loco set of the soldado nation gang.
我们知道 第一 洛沃斯有一个
We learned that, one, Lobos has one single distributor
给纽约供货的批发商
for his product in New York City.
第二 他对他的经销商不是很满意
Two, he's not entirely happy with his distributor.
第三 索尔达多族和鲁伊斯
And three, soldado nation and Ruiz
都在低价为洛沃斯工作
are too low-rent for Lobos.
他们的关系还没铁到可以为他发货
They're not organized enough to distribute his product.
而且他也不介意告诉鲁伊斯
And he was not shy in telling Mr. Ruiz
他屁都不在乎
he did not give a fuck!
我们得到了墨西哥政府
We have permission from the Mexican government
拘留和诉讼洛沃斯的许可
to detain and prosecute Mr. Lobos
如果我们想对他建立有力的调查
if we can build a compelling case against him.
我们就不能惊动它
We can't touch him unless we know
直到我们确定可以逮捕他
we can put him in jail.
谁能给我们提供能给洛沃斯判罪相关的
Who can give us the names, places, and dates
人名 地点 和日期?
we need to convict Lobos?
他在纽约的批发商
His New York distributor.
很不幸我们不知道那是谁
Unfortunately we have no idea who that is.
我们有一份我们所需要的
We do have a profile of the type of criminal
关于这个嫌疑人的介绍
we're looking for.
他是个十分有条理的人
He's a highly organized individual
拥有已经建立好的关系网络
with an established network in place.
他已经了解怎么将钱在系统中转移
He already knows how to move money through the system,
足够暴力能控制它的领地
is violent enough to control his territory,
但他还有可被掌控的一些地方
but still has something to lose...
一些洛沃斯可以威胁让他乖乖听话的理由
something Lobos can threaten to keep him in line.
所以为什么洛沃斯想要换掉他?
So why is Lobos looking to replace him?
发生了什么问题?
What could've gone wrong?
一定有些因素他无法掌控
There must be some element out of his control.
莉莉安娜
我送完最后一票了
我这就过来
不管因为什么 这个洛沃斯和他当地人
Whatever the reason, this problem
之间的问题
between Lobos and his local guy
正是我们所要查明的
is exactly what we need to exploit,
因为我们要找的这个人已经陷入
because the man we're looking for is in grave danger...
来自洛沃斯和我们的严峻危险...
from Lobos and from us.
我们可以给他一条生路
We can give him a way out,
但只有当他决定接受的时候
but only if he decides to take it.
汤米什么事? 我这就去
Tommy, what's up? I'm on my way.